(212) 658-0618

Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

[Home](https://carpetcleaningnyc.com/) — Privacy Policy

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
--------------------------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.  
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.  
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Your Consent
------------

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

service@carpetcleaningnyc.com

#### Recent Posts

#### Our Locations

#### BUSINESS HOURS

Mon: 8:00 AM – 6:00 PM  
Tue:   8:00 AM – 6:00 PM  
Wed: 8:00 AM – 6:00 PM  
Thu:  8:00 AM – 6:00 PM  
Fri:    8:00 AM – 6:00 PM  
Sat:    8:00 AM –  6:00 PM  
Sun:  10:00 AM – 5:00 PM

#### COMPANY INFO

My Home  
Carpet Cleaning NYC  
New York, NY 10016, USA  
Phone:(212) 658-0618

#### Recent Posts

#### BUSINESS HOURS

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Mon: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |
| Tue: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |
| Wed: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |
| Thu: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |
| Fri: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |
| Sat: | Closed |
| Sun: | 8:00 AM – 5:00 PM |

#### NYC AREAS

#### INFO LINKS

2023 My Home Carpet Cleaning NYC. All rights of content are protected
